What?!
(紅蓮)なに!?
(麟児)ヘッ 結界を破りやがった。
They broke the barrier.
They're not bad.
(麟児)敵も なかなか
やるじゃねえか。
Guren...
(牛頭)紅蓮さん…。
(麟児)あっ おい！
Huh? H-Hey!
Kakashi-sensei!
(サクラ)カカシ先生！
(紅蓮)フン 新手か。
Humph! Back up, huh?
Is everybody all right?
(ナルト)大丈夫か？ みんな。
(カカシ)ナルト 今のは？
Naruto, what was that...?
That was Collaboration Ninjutsu with a toad.
We learned it from Pervy Sage.
エロ仙人に教わった
ガマとのコラボ忍術だ。
Oh...!
ほう。
Now! It's my turn!
You! There's nowhere to escape!
さ～て 暴れるぜ！
いいか！ もう逃げらんねえぞ！
フン また ずいぶんと
騒がしいのが現れたね。
Here comes that really loud guy!
ヒナタ！
Hinata!
You! What did you do to Hinata?!
お前 ヒナタに 何しやがった！
What are you going to do,
Kakashi-sensei?!
どうするんだよ カカシ先生。
We can't attack them recklessly
since Hinata has been taken hostage.
(カカシ)ヒナタが人質に
とられている以上➡
うかつに手は出せない。
Besides, any small shock will
cause that crystal to shatter.
そのうえ あの結晶は
少しの衝撃で➡
ヒナタもろとも粉々に崩れる。
(ヤマト)やっかいですね。
What a mess.
(ヤマト)サイ 相手の隙を見て➡
- Sai, wait for your chance...
- You realize your situation,
- to attack from the sky.
- so just return to the Leaf!
キミは 上空から。
(サイ)はい。
Right!
- Gamatatsu, can you do that once more?
- If you go back, I'll let this kid go.
ガマ竜 もう一度いけるか？
Yeah... just one more time...
(ガマ竜)うん あと一発なら。
I must control my Wind Chakra
so Hinata won't get hurt.
《ヒナタに当てねえように
風のチャクラは おさえねえと》
Freeze!
動くな！
今だ ガマ竜！
- Now, Gamatatsu!
- Stop, Naruto!
Wind Style: Toad Water Pistol!
(カカシ)やめろ ナルト！
風遁 ガマ鉄砲！
なに!?
What?!
My Crystal Style can crystallize all materials.
私の晶遁は
すべての物質を結晶化する。
You need ten more years of experience
before you can challenge me.
私に挑もうなんて
10年早いんだよ。
Crystal Style: Burst Crystal Falling Dragon.
晶遁 破晶降龍。
Gamatatsu, run away!
(ガマ吉)ガマ竜 逃げろ！
大丈夫か？ みんな。
(サイ/サクラ)はい！
Is everyone safe?
- Yes!
Damn it! What was that?!
クソ… なんだよ あれ！
She crystallized your Jutsu
and turned it into her own Jutsu.
お前の術を結晶化して
自分の術にしたんだ。
Listen, Naruto! I'll get her attention.
いいか ナルト。 オレが ヤツの気を引く。
You protect Hinata,
then pull out from the battle!
その隙に ヒナタを保護して
戦線を離脱しろ。
- What?!
- Hinata's life is the top priority right now.
えっ！
(カカシ)今は ヒナタの命が最優先だ。
あぁ。
(紅蓮)隠れてもムダだよ。
Right.
It's useless to hide.
Don't forget I have a hostage!
こっちには人質がいることを
忘れんじゃないよ！
フン あきらめたようだね。
They seem to have given up.
Let Hinata go.
Take me as your hostage instead.
ヒナタを返してもらおう。
かわりに オレが人質になる。
えっ!?
What?!
That's wishful thinking!
甘いんだよ！
Now, Naruto!
ナルト 今だ！
ガマ竜！
Gamatatsu!
I won't let you get away!
逃がすか！
チクショウ… 汚れちまった。
Damn it! My clothes are so filthy now.
Guren-san!
(牛頭)紅蓮さん。
大丈夫ですか？
あぁ。
- Are you all right?
- Yeah...
I'm relieved.
(麟児)ご無事で何より。
ヘッ… ったく 逃げ足の速い連中だ。
I must say, they ran away rather quickly.
Rinji, don't lose track of them!
麟児！ 監視の手を
ゆるめるんじゃないよ！
はい。
All right.
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
The Target Appears
もういいぞ ガマ竜。
ヒナタを出してやってくれ。
All right, Gamatatsu,
you can bring Hinata out now.
ガマ竜！ そっと そっとじゃぞ。
Gamatatsu! Gently, gently!
そ～っと そ～っと…。
Gently, gently.
Good! Just like that, slowly, slowly.
いいぞ そのまま
ゆっくり ゆっくり…。
Oh!
A fly!
(ガマ竜)あっ ハエ！
(サイ/サクラ)あっ！
(キバ)ヒナタ！
Hinata!
You fool! What are you doing, idiot?!
どアホ！ 何しよんじゃ このボケ！
えっ… そんな… ダメだ！ 止まれ！
Huh?!
No! Stop! Please stop!
止まってくれ！
ヒナタ！
Hinata!
(赤丸)ワン！
と 止まった。
It... stopped...
Damn! We're too late...
(パックン)しまった 遅かったか。
(カカシ)パックン。
Pakkun!
(パックン)シノの寄壊蟲の分析が
終了した。
They finished analyzing
Shino's Parasitic Insect.
敵の術は
晶遁に間違いないようじゃ。
It appears the enemy's Jutsu
was definitely the Crystal Style.
(カカシ)やはり…。
Just as we suspected...
寄壊蟲の周りを覆っていた
結晶からは➡
And the analyst confirmed
that several materials from the crystal
encased the Parasitic Insect.
いくつかの物質が
確認された。
(カカシ)すべての物質を
結晶化するという言葉は➡
It was true what she said about it
crystallizing all materials.
本当だったようだな。
Sai's Super Beast Scroll was also crystallized.
It's a troublesome Jutsu.
サイの超獣偽画も
結晶化してましたし➡
やっかいな術ですね。
Not only the Jutsu itself, but also its effects.
やっかいなのは
術そのものではなく➡
その効力じゃ。
(シノ)それは もしや…。
ああ➡
- So, that means...
- Right...
They said that even the biological fluid
of the Parasitic Insect was crystallized.
寄壊蟲の体液すら
結晶化していたそうじゃ。
What?! Then...
じゃあ…。
なぁ ヒナタは…➡
And Hinata?
Is Hinata all right, Kakashi-sensei?
ヒナタは 大丈夫だよな？ カカシ先生。
あ あぁ…。
Y-Yeah...
We should take her
to the village immediately.
急いで 里に運ぶ必要があるね。
I know! Grandma Tsunade!
Grandma will help her.
そうだ 綱手のばあちゃん➡
ばあちゃんなら
なんとかしてくれるよな！
落ち着け ナルト。
Calm down, Naruto!
ヒナタ！
Hinata!
サクラ…。
Sakura...!
大丈夫 生きてます。
Don't worry! She's alive.
- Are you sure?
- What a relief!
ホントか!?
よかった。
あぁ ビックリしたね。
Wow, that scared me...
Idiot! How can you be so distracted
by a mere fly?!
アホ！ ハエなんかに
気とられおって！
Wha--?
What's the matter, Shino?
どうした？ シノ。
オレの蟲たちのことを
考えていた。
I was thinking about my Parasitic Insects...
(シノ)晶遁の術にやられた蟲は➡
After it was defeated by
the Crystal Style Jutsu,
the insect shattered in my hand.
オレの手の中で砕けた。
なのに ヒナタは助かった。
And yet, Hinata survived...
確かに 最初に
オレたちが目撃した晶遁も➡
True. When we first encountered
the Crystal Style, it shattered.
結晶の粉となり 砕けた。
生き残った蟲と ヒナタには
何か 共通点があるってことか。
I wonder what the insect that survived
and Hinata have in common?
(ヒナタ)私…。
いきなり動かないで。
I...
Oh, don't move so soon.
(ヒナタ)
私 術を受けたとき とっさに➡
When I received the Jutsu...
I released my Chakra from
my Chakra Points all at once,
点穴からチャクラを放ち➡
体の表面に
薄い膜を作ったんです。
to make a thin film in which
to cover myself.
I see. That's why, even her Crystal Style
failed to crystallize Chakra.
(シノ)なるほど ヤツの晶遁でも➡
チャクラを結晶化することは
出来なかったというわけか。
Although you faced the unexpected,
you did a great job, Hinata.
うん とっさの判断とはいえ
よくやったな ヒナタ。
はい。
Right...
Only a Hyuga family member could pull that off.
Hinata, you're awesome!
さすがだぜ！
すげえじゃねえか ヒナタ。
ワン！
I'm glad you're okay.
無事でよかったな。
ご ごめんね ナルト君
心配かけちゃったね。
Sorry you had to worry about me, Naruto...
お前が 謝る必要なんて
ねえってばよ。
You don't need to apologize.
Naruto...
ナルト君…。
さてと先輩
どうしますか？ これから。
Well, Senpai, what are we going to do now?
うん… そうだな。
Well... Let's see...
わ 私なら 大丈夫です。
I-I'm all right.
まだ ムリしちゃダメよ。
Don't force yourself just yet.
(シノ)晶遁にやられたのが
まだ ヒナタでよかった。
I think we were lucky because Hinata
was the only victim of the Crystal Style...
We don't have any countermeasures
against the Crystal Style at this point,
晶遁の対抗策がない今➡
いったん引くというのも
勇気ある行動だ。
so retreating is the best option for now.
But then, they'll get away!
けど それじゃ
ヤツらに逃げられちまう。
Right. Unless we stay on the look out,
we'll lose them.
(カカシ)あぁ 確かに 今ここで
ヤツらから目を離せば➡
見失ってしまう。
It was so much trouble finding them.
(キバ)見つけんのに オレたち
あんだけ苦労したんだ。
ここで ヤツらを逃がしちまうと
また見つけられるかどうか。
I'm afraid that if we let them go now,
we'll never find them again...
(カカシ)なら こうしよう。
Then here's the plan.
We have enough members,
so let's split into two groups.
人数もいることだし
二班に分ける。
サイとサクラは ヒナタの回復を待って
ここで待機。
Sai and Sakura, you two stand by here
to wait for Hinata's recovery.
(サイ/サクラ)はい。
(カカシ)他の者は 追跡班だ。
- Right!
The others will track them.
と いっても 連中は
ニオイを消しながら逃げている。
But as they move,
they're erasing their scent.
赤丸でも追跡不可能だ。
It's impossible to track them,
even for Akamaru.
It looks like they're extremely cautious.
かなりの念の入れようですね。
そんじゃあ 追跡不可能なヤツらを
どうやって見つけんだ？
Then how can we find someone
that seems so impossible to track?
(カカシ)ヤツらの
監視用コウモリを利用させてもらう。
We can use their monitoring bats.
ただし コウモリに近づきすぎると➡
However, if we get too close to a bat,
they'll find us first.
逆に こちらが見つかってしまう。
だから慎重に進むしかない。
So we should be very careful
from this point on.
なるほど。
めんどくせえけど 仕方ねえか。
I see...
It's a pain, but we don't have a choice...
(カカシ)それだけじゃない。
I have something to add.
We also should be careful about the
Crystal Style barrier which Naruto just broke.
さっきナルトが壊した
晶遁の結界にも注意が必要だ。
(カカシ)もし ヤツらを発見しても
絶対に手を出さないこと。
Even if you find them, don't attack.
After all, our goal is to investigate them.
あくまで オレたちの目的は
ヤツらを探ることにある。
(みんな)了解。
- Understood!
Then we're going home.
それじゃ ワシらはボチボチ帰るけん。
ああ また頼むぜ。
We'll see you the next time
we need your help.
I'm going home too, Kakashi.
拙者も帰らせてもらうぞ カカシ。
Good work today, Pakkun.
ああ パックン お疲れさん。
じゃあのぉ。
それじゃ バイバ～イ。
- See you!
- Good bye!
Then let's go, everyone!
(カカシ)さて 我々も行くぞ。
(幽鬼丸)紅蓮さん。
Guren-san!
(紅蓮)なにも変わったことは
なかったか？
Is everything all right?
知ってる人に会いました。
なに？
I ran into someone I know.
誰なんだ？
What?
Who was that?
(幽鬼丸)額当てをしてた。
額当て？
The man with the headband.
Headband?
まさか さっきの連中。
Could it be the guy we just met?
どうして ソイツが
お前の知り合いなんだ？
How do you know about him?
う～ん。
Well... That's right!
そう 前にカブトさんと
出かけたときに会ったの。
When I went out with Kabuto-san the other day,
I met him.
その人は帰るべき場所があるって。
The man said he has a place to return to.
だから一緒に帰ろうって
言われたんだけど➡
And he asked me to return with him,
but I didn't.
ボク やめたんだ。
だってきっと
ボクの帰る場所は違うから。
Because I thought that was not
the kind of place where I could return to.
偶然か？
(麟児)ああ➡
Was that just coincidence?
I think so. Because there's no way
they saw us and this kid together.
ヤツらは オレたちとコイツが
一緒のところは➡
見てないはずだしな。
さて どうします 紅蓮さん？
Well, what should we do, Guren-sann?
決まってる。
There can only be one answer.
いいぞ よく戻ってきた。
Good boy, thanks for coming back.
お前の帰るべき場所は
ソイツらじゃない。
It's not them to whom you return,
but to me.
私のところだ。
うん。
(紅蓮)ただ お前の知り合いなら
挨拶しとかなきゃな。
Yeah.
But if he's your friend,
I want to say hello to him.
ソイツは どこにいたんだ？
Where did you see him?
(麟児)ヤツらを追うんですね。
ああ。
Are you going to track them?
Yes.
(紅蓮)
一度狙った獲物は逃がさない。
Once I decide to go after something,
I stick with it.
それが私のやり方だ。
That's the way I do things.
(カブト)紅蓮 悪いクセが出たな。
Guren, that's a bad habit.
(幽鬼丸)カブトさん。
Kabuto-san!
(カブト)そうやって すぐ調子に乗る。
なんだと！
- It's easy for you to go overboard.
-What?!
少しは反省してもらいたいね。
I hope you have some remorse.
今の話で幽鬼丸が連中に
拉致されなかったのは ラッキーだ。
Based on the story I just heard,
I think you were very lucky that
they didn't take Yuukimaru away.
もし ここで幽鬼丸を失うような
ことがあれば➡
If you lose Yuukimaru...
紅蓮
キミは大蛇丸様の信用を失うよ。
Guren, you'll lose credibility
with Orochimaru-sama.
悪いがキミたちは ここに残って
木ノ葉の連中を警戒してくれ。
Sorry, but you guys must stay here
and watch out for the guys
from the Hidden Leaf.
今度のことは 誰にも
ジャマされたくはないんだ。
We don't want any distractions.
なんだよ オレたちは行けねえのか。
What?! We can't come with you?!
麟児 ここは
カブトの言うことを聞きな。
Rinji, this time just follow
what Kabuto says!
わかりました。
紅蓮さんが言うんじゃ。
All right. If you say so, Guren-san...
悪いね。 じゃあ 出してくれ。
Sorry...
Let's go.
ここから先は 人数が少なければ
少ないほどいい。
From now on,
the fewer people, the better.
何か見られちゃ
まずいものでもあるのか？
Is there something that
you don't want us to see?
まあ 滅多に見られるものじゃ
ないのは確かだね。
Well, there's something
you don't see very often.
見てのお楽しみさ。
Just wait until you see it.
どうした？
カブトさん➡
What's the matter?
Kabuto-san... I have a bad feeling...
ちょっと イヤだな。
薬を飲んだ時
すごく頭が痛くなって…。
When I took the medicine,
my head really hurt.
大丈夫だ。
悪いことには ならないよ。
Don't worry. Nothing will go wrong.
何かあったら
紅蓮さんが守ってくれる。
When something happens,
Guren-san will protect you.
ホント？
- Really?
- Y-Yeah. That's true.
あぁ… 本当だ。
クッソ…➡
Damn it! We shouldn't have taken
our eyes off them, even for a moment!
やっぱり 一瞬でも
目を離したのが まずかったぜ。
また 一からヤツらの気配を
探さなきゃならねえ！
We have to start tracking them
all over again!
コウモリのせいで 自由に動けないのが
いてえってばよ！
Because of the bats,
we can't move freely!
こうなったら
一か八かの方法を試すか…。
We have no choice.
Shall we try it the risky way?
シノ 何か手があるのか？
Shino, do you have an idea?
考え方の問題だ。
Let's change our way of thinking.
見つからないように
している場合➡
Not wanting the bats to find us
is a problem.
コウモリは 確かに障害となる。
だが 見つかることを
覚悟していれば➡
But if we assume the bats will find us,
we can take advantage of them.
コウモリは利用できる。
ん？ どういうことだってばよ。
Huh? What does that mean?
コウモリの超音波は
そう遠くへは届かない。
The supersonic waves of the bats
won't work far away.
ようするに
オレたちの居場所を感知したあと➡
When the bats sense our presence,
how do they report it to the enemy?
どうやって ヤツらに知らせてるか
を考えれば…。
なるほど そういうことか。
Oh, I get it now!
言われてみれば そのとおりだ。
Now that you mention it, you're right.
よく気づいたな シノ。
Good work figuring it out, Shino.
ちょ… ちょっと待って。
H-Hold on!
Does everyone understand?
みんな わかったのか？
当たり前だろ。 ここにいるのは
全員が上忍と中忍だぞ。
Who doesn't understand?
We're all Chunin and Jonin.
…っと １名 まだ下忍だったな。
Oops! There's one Genin.
テメエ ケンカうってんのか！
You, are you trying to pick a fight?!
Fine! I understand, too!
フン いいよ！ オレだって
理由は わかったもんな！
ん？ ホントか～？
Really?
話を戻そう。 で どうする？
Let's get back to what
we were talking about.
So, what should we do?
(カカシ)やってみよう！ ナルト！
Let's try it!
３人の影分身を作って➡
Naruto, make three Shadow Clones,
幅10メートルの間隔を取りながら
地上を走らせろ！
line them up ten meters away
from each other
and have them run around the grounds!
えっ そんなことしたら…。
(カカシ)早くしろ！
But if I do that...
Hurry up!
ったく わかったってばよ！
I know!
影分身の術！
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
こんなことしたら コウモリのレーダーに
引っかかっちまうだろう。
But won't the bats' radar detect us
if I do this?!
それでいいんだ。
えっ？
- That's what we want!
- What?
あれだ！ なぜなら➡
I found them! That must be it!
昼間に理由なく コウモリが
飛び立つなど 有り得ないからだ。
Because there's no reason
for the bats to be flying around
during the daytime without
a good reason.
よし 行くぞ みんな！
All right! Let's go, everyone!
ところでよ みんな
なんで コウモリ追いかけてんだ？
By the way,
why are we following the bats?
だぁ～…
やっぱ わかってねえのかよ！
Duh! See, you don't understand, do you?!
あのコウモリは オレたちを見つけた
ってことを知らせに➡
Those bats will return to their hideout
to let them know they've found us!
ヤツらのところに
戻ってるんだよ！
ん？
つまり アイツを追っていけば
敵に たどりつけるってことだ。
Um...?
That means, if we follow them,
we'll find where the enemy is hiding.
なんだ そんなことか！
Oh, I get it!
ったく… ホント
いつまでも ダメダメだな お前は。
Good grief! You're still no good.
Humph! Stop being so bossy,
just because you're a Chunin!
中忍になったからって
偉そうなことを言いやがって！
これでも くらえ！
Take this!
うわぁ～!!
くっせ～！
That stinks!
ヘヘッ ざま～みろ！
Heh, heh! Look at yourself!
《何度来ても不気味な場所だ…》
Every time I come to this place,
I feel really weird...
(牛頭)ここで 何をするんだ？
What are you going to do here?
なに… ちょっとした実験だよ。
Well... I'll perform a little test.
彼と紅蓮を使ってね。
With him and... Guren.
さぁ これをかぶって。
Here, put this on.
そんな量を飲ませたら…。
If you give him that much medicine...!
Huh?
お前は 大蛇丸様の計画を
ジャマする気か？
Are you trying to disrupt
Orochimaru-sama's plan?
((大蛇丸 : この仕事はね➡
I really must have you for this mission.
どうしても あなたに
やってもらいたいのよ。
いいえ あなたにしか
できない仕事よ。
In fact, you're the only one who can do it.
私にしか…？
Only me?
(大蛇丸)そうしたら
もう一度 考えてみてもいいわよ。
Then perhaps, I may want to reconsider...
(私の器に いちばん
ふさわしいのは誰か…))
who is the best suited to become my vessel.
安心していい。
さぁ おもしろいことを始めよう。
Don't worry. Let's start something fun.
前 飲んだ薬とは違う。
苦しくはならないようにしてある。
This medicine is different from
what you took before.
This medicine won't bring you
any suffering.
これを飲まないと
いつまでも帰れないよ。
You can't go back until you take this.
(カブト)さぁ 紅蓮 お前の番だ。
(紅蓮)いちいち命令するな！
Guren, it's your turn.
Stop being so bossy all the time!
晶遁 翠晶六角柱！
Crystal Style:
Jade Crystal Hexagonal Column!
あっ！
Oh!
あぁ…。
フゥー。
《何だ？ 何が始まる》
What? What is going to happen?
うっ！ うぅ～っ！
うわぁ～!!
《この気配は…》
What is this...?
気をつけな。 くるよ！
Be careful! It's coming!
くる!?
It's coming?
実験は成功だ！ 現れるぞ！
The test was successful!
It'll appear!
何が現れるんだ!?
What will appear?!
尾獣だよ。
尾獣!?
A Tailed Beast.
Tailed Beast...?
This is the Three-Tailed Beast.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
Next Episode
フフフ…。
What's that feeling...?
うわぁ～!!
What's the matter, Shino?
My insects... feel a weird Chakra.
Weird Chakra?
(カブト)コイツが三尾だ。
They've never felt so much Chakra before.
It looks like Akamaru feels
the same thing as your insects!
What's going on over there?!
Let's hurry, we'll go straight through!
The Rampaging Tailed Beast
Next Time: "The Rampaging Tailed Beast"
あっ！ 何これ… がん細胞!?
Wh-What're these? Cancer cells?
[無線](シノ)あぁ すまん。
- Ah! Sorry.
- What...?!
ヘヘヘーン！
オレ ちょっと体重 増えたぜ。
- Ahem! I put on some weight.
- I gained weight, too.
オレだって増えたぜ。
(サイ)ボクは あまり変わらないや。
My weight hasn't changed much...
(シノ)フゥー。
そんなのを比べて どうする。
Why are you comparing them?
(キバ)シノ…。
Shino?
あっ おい
お前 服着たままじゃ…。
Oh! Hey, you still have your clothes on...
(シノ)服の重さは関係ない。
なぜなら➡
It doesn't matter how heavy my clothes are...
because I can control my weight,
depending on how many insects I have.
蟲の数によって
いくらでも調整が可能だからだ。
へぇ～ 便利だ。
ひぃ～！
Wow, it's so convenient.
56.6キロ。
今日は このくらいにしておこう。
56.6 kg... Not bad for today.
体重計の…。
(２人)意味ねえだろ！
- You don't need...
- a scale!
"To be continued"